Guide to the Fulton Theater Records, 1934-1963 CTC.2000.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Movie Files and Promotional Materials, 1944-1963; IV.
  - Torrid Zone, Warner Brothers, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Undertow, Universal, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Wake Up and Dream, 20th Century Fox, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Wake of the Red Witch, Republic, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Without Honor, United Artists, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Wonder Man, RKO, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Wyoming, Republic, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Young Widow, United Artists, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - You're My Everything, 20th Century Fox, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Film summaries and reviews A-I (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Film summaries and reviews J-Z (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Film Service press releases, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 3)